[festive music playing]
[choir singing]
[clears throat]
[inhales deeply]
[crowing]
[groans]
[wind whooshing]
[squeaking]
[static on radio]
[upbeat festive music playing]
[both exclaiming excitedly]
♪ It's that time of the year
Where the holly is hung ♪
♪ We give a little love ♪
♪ Festive plans and helping hands… ♪
Whee! [chuckles]
♪ It's Christmas! ♪
♪ Can you hear the sleigh in the sky? ♪
[grunts]
♪ Make a wish and close your eyes… ♪
Oh…
[clucking]
♪ Chestnuts roasting
And marshmallows toasting ♪
♪ Let's put the year under the tree ♪
♪ Bells are jingling… ♪
[bleats]
♪ Sing songs merrily ♪
[all bleating excitedly]
♪ Bells are jingling, ooh… ♪
-[exclaims]
-[all cheering]
♪ The bells are jingling… ♪
[music stops abruptly]
-[electricity crackles]
-[Bitzer chuckles]
[sighs]
[bleats disapprovingly]
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Hmm…
[triumphant music playing]
[chuckles]
[exclaims]
[bleats]
[bleating]
-[bleats]
-[Timmy] Hmm?
[grunts]
[bleats questioningly]
[bleats reassuringly]
[Shaun and Timmy chuckling]
[bleats]
[The Farmer humming]
[whimsical music playing]
-[The Farmer] Hmm?
-[chuckling]
[mumbling]
[chuckles]
[kisses]
[The Farmer] Mmm.
Ah!
[sniffs] Ooh!
Hmm?
[man on laptop chuckling] Eh?
[grunts]
[bubbling]
Ah.
-[bubbling]
-Mmm-hmm.
Oh!
[The Farmer grunts]
Hmm.
Er…
-[glitching]
-Er…
[mumbling]
[gasps]
-[grunts]
-[The Farmer gasps]
-[bubbling]
-[both gasp]
[exclaims] Ah!
[slurps]
Oh! [gags]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[menacing music plays]
[music stops]
-[squeaking]
-[sighs]
Ah!
Huh? [chuckles]
Er… [grunts]
[bubbling]
[squeaks]
[The Farmer] Ah! Mmm-hmm.
-[Bitzer grunts]
-Ho-ho-ho!
[Bitzer groaning]
[chuckles]
-[bleats]
-[Timmy] Hmm?
-[Timmy grunts]
[pulley squeaking]
Hmm?
[enchanting music playing]
-Ooh!
-[grunts]
[gags]
-[Shaun chuckles]
-[door slams]
-[both gasp]
-[Shaun] Mmm?
-[Timmy] Mmm?
-[exclaims]
[The Farmer speaking indistinctly]
[scoffs]
[grunts]
[Timmy grunts]
[shuddering]
[footsteps approaching]
[ominous music playing]
[jingling]
Ho-ho! [chuckling]
[sighs] Huh?
[Shaun gulps]
Hmm.
[chuckles]
[Timmy bleats]
[gasps]
Ho-ho-ho!
[grunts]
-[giggling]
-[Shaun groans]
[effort grunts]
Whoa…
[grunts]
Ah. [grunts]
[sighs]
[bleats]
[The Farmer grunts]
Ho ho ho!
-[gasps]
-[captivating music playing]
[The Farmer] Ah.
[bleats]
[grunts]
[giggling]
Ha!
Huh…
[grunts]
Huh?
[gasps]
-Ah!
-[grunts]
-[groans]
-Ah.
-[mumbles]
-[grunts]
[Timmy grunts]
[Shaun] Hmm? [grunts]
-Huh?
-[Timmy grunting]
[engine starts]
-[bleats]
-[sinister music playing]
[Timmy bleats]
[Timmy's Mother] Oh!
[gasps]
[Timmy's Mother exclaiming]
[bleats]
[bleating angrily]
[Shaun] Hmm?
Hmm.
-[bells chiming]
-[crowd exclaiming]
[all applauding]
[both mumbling]
Oh!
[chuckling] Huh?
[sighs]
[groans]
-[chuckles]
-Eee!
-[crowd cheering]
[all] Three… two… one!
[exclaiming]
[chuckles]
[all cheering]
[festive music playing]
[laughing]
[gasps]
[kisses]
-[laughs and mumbles]
-[Bitzer] Hmm?
Hmm.
-[laughs]
-[gasps]
[gasping]
[clinking]
[gasps]
-[victorious music playing]
-Ho-ho!
[whimpering]
-[The Farmer mumbles]
-Huh?
[sighs]
[horn honks]
[indistinct chatter]
-[man exclaims]
-[engine stops]
[all mumbling]
[Shaun] Hmm.
[child chuckles]
[Shaun giggles]
[Bitzer sighs]
-[clothing squeaks]
-[scratches]
[Shaun gasps]
[bleats]
[The Flock bleating]
[Bitzer mumbles]
[sighs]
Huh?
[mumbles]
-[mumbles]
-[suspenseful music plays]
-[Bitzer grunting]
-[The Flock chuckling]
[mumbles]
Huh.
[exclaiming]
[all gasp]
[bleating]
[Shaun sighs]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[Timmy] Hmm.
[enchanting music playing]
[cheering]
[Shaun] Hmm.
-[Timmy's Mother bleats]
-Hmm?
Ah… ah!
-[gasps]
-[woman gasps]
[mumbling angrily]
[all clamouring]
-[creaking]
-[Shirley] Oh.
-[The Farmer mumbling]
-[Shirley shouts]
Oh! [exclaiming]
[mumbling]
-[exclaiming]
-[man] Ooh.
-Ta-da!
-[woman gasps]
-Huh?
-Hmm?
-[festive music playing]
-[clanging]
-[trumpet plays off-key]
-[gasps]
[gasps]
[trumpets]
[all grunting]
[mumbling angrily]
-[groans]
-[cocks trumpet]
-[all gasping]
-[The Farmer] Hmm.
[grunts]
-[Bitzer] Er…
-[crowd grumbling]
[whimpers]
Huh? [gasps]
[whistles]
[grunting]
Hmm.
[sighs and gasps]
[all shouting]
[screams]
[Ella mumbling]
[Shaun] Hmm. Hmm?
[The Farmer grunting]
-[children screaming]
-[The Farmer screaming] Ooh!
[gasps]
[children screaming]
[grunting]
[Timmy] Hmm.
-[groans]
-[children laughing]
-Hey! [chuckling]
-[child cheering]
[Timmy gasps]
[chuckles]
[chuckling]
-[Shaun gasps]
-[bleats]
-[The Farmer sighs]
-[clears throat] Huh?
[The Farmer] Oh. Er…
-[gasps and exclaims]
-Huh?
[gasps]
-[chuckles]
-[The Farmer groans]
[grunts]
-[mumbles]
-Ha!
[gasps]
Ho ho ho… [groaning]
[sighs]
[bleats softly]
[Ella exclaims]
-[Timmy's Mother] Oh!
-[all gasp]
[ominous music playing]
[Jin] Bye!
[bleats worriedly]
-[engine starts]
-[Timmy whimpers]
-[bleats sadly]
-[Shaun sighs]
[children chuckling]
-[car horn honking]
-[gasps]
[grunts angrily]
[huffs]
-[bleating in distance]
-Hmm?
[dramatic music playing]
-[bleating]
-[yelps]
-[crashing]
-Oh!
[bleating]
[chuckles]
Huh?
[growling]
-[grunts]
-[coins clattering]
[whooshing]
[The Flock exclaiming]
[Bitzer exclaiming]
[upbeat music playing]
[all bleating]
[bleats]
[all gasping]
[gasps]
[both shrieking]
[chuckles]
-[bleats]
-[creaking]
[engine revving]
[grunting]
[gasps]
Huh?
[Timmy bleats softly]
[all bleating]
[Ben humming]
[wind blowing]
[Jin] Oh.
[all bleating]
[Jin] Hmm.
[grunting]
[gasps]
♪ We're walking in the-- ♪
[yelling]
[Bitzer continues yelling]
[bleating]
[groans]
[grunting]
[water sloshing]
Er…
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[chuckling]
[grunts]
[beep]
[whirring and beeping]
Ah.
[all gasp]
[exclaims excitedly]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[gasps] Huh?
Uh-uh.
-[chuckles]
-[gasps]
[sighs]
Hmm. Ugh.
Er…
[gasps] Huh?
[chuckles]
[mischievous music playing]
[giggling] Huh?
[sighs]
-Eee!
-[Jin] Mmm.
[twangs]
[groans]
-Hmm.
-[hair twangs]
[gasps]
[groans]
[mumbles]
[switch clicks]
[door closes]
-[knocking on window]
-Huh?
[bleats excitedly]
-[bleats excitedly]
-[Shaun] Mmm.
[effort grunting]
[bleats softly]
[Shaun grunts]
[pensive music playing]
[Shaun] Hmm.
[all whispering indistinctly]
[Ella humming]
[pants excitedly]
[chuckling]
[exclaims and sighs]
[Ben mumbling]
-[mumbles]
-Hmm?
-Ah.
-[giggles]
[chuckles]
Mmm… Ha! [giggles]
[exclaims]
[both chuckling]
[sighs]
Hmm.
[device beeps]
Huh?
[mumbling]
[reading indistinctly]
[mumbles and kisses]
[door closes]
[groans] Hmm.
Ha!
[whistling]
-[doorbell rings]
-Oh.
[indistinct singing]
[singing and bleating]
[groans]
[singing and bleating continues]
[door locking]
[all sighing]
-[Shaun] Hmm.
-[Shirley exclaims]
[mumbling]
Hmm? [effort grunts]
[ripping]
[gasps]
Hmm.
[hinges creaking]
Oh!
[chuckling]
[bleats]
Huh? [grunts]
Whoa!
[rumbling]
[all yelling and bleating]
[thudding]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[groans]
[growling angrily]
[sighs]
-[chirps]
-Huh?
Oh!
-[chirps]
-[gasping]
[sneezes]
[groans]
[sniffles and sighs]
Huh? Ah!
[chuckles]
-[grunting]
-[ice crackling]
Aha!
[ice shattering]
[groans]
[whimsical music playing]
[chuckles]
-[grunts]
-[switch clicks]
[bubbling]
[effort grunts]
[sighs]
-[chuckles] Huh?
-[crackling]
[gasps]
[grunting]
Aha!
-[clicks]
-[machine whirring]
-[sighs]
-[sizzling]
Ah.
-[water trickling]
-[chuckles]
-[electricity crackles]
-Huh?
[yelling]
[sizzling]
[groaning]
[sighs]
[electricity buzzing]
[grate clatters]
[grunts]
[hinges creaking]
[scoffs]
-[Roomba whirring]
-Hmm?
-[beeping]
-[groans]
[Jin yelps]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[Ben] Er… Oh! [clicks tongue]
Hmm.
[Jin] Mmm…
Mmm.
[both] Aha. Ah!
Phew.
[sighs in relief]
[gasps]
[Ella chuckling]
[sighs]
[hopeful music playing]
[Timmy bleats]
[whimpers]
Huh.
-[whimpers]
-[Ella] Ha!
Huh?
Ooh.
Whoa!
Huh.
Hmm.
[bleating]
[exclaims]
-[bleats]
-[gasps]
-[chuckles]
-[bleats]
[Ella grunts]
[grunts]
-[sighs]
-[yells]
[chuckles]
[whimpers]
[toy roaring]
[chuckling]
[sinister music plays]
[Shaun gasping]
[groaning]
[Timmy's Mother whimpers]
[grunts] Hmm.
[gasps]
[groans]
["Silent Night" playing over headphones]
-[exclaims]
-[Shaun grunts]
-[all bleating]
-[upbeat music playing]
[bleats]
Oh!
[bleating orders]
-[water bubbling]
-Hmm?
-["Silent Night" continues playing]
-[chomps]
[grunts]
-[upbeat music continues]
-[bleats]
[Shaun] Oh!
-[mobile ringing]
-[bleats]
[mumbling]
-Huh?
-[bleats]
-Er…
[line disconnects]
[bleats]
[Ella exclaiming excitedly]
Whee! [chuckling]
Whee!
[bleating orders]
[thudding]
-[bleating]
-[all gasping]
[bleating orders]
["Silent Night" continues over headphones]
[doorknob rattles]
-[Ella sighs]
-[gasps]
-[bleating]
-[whispers]
Shh.
[suspenseful music playing]
[whimpering]
[sighs]
[Timmy's Mother exclaims]
[both bleating happily]
[Ella groaning]
[sighs]
[toy roaring]
[Ella sighs]
[all sighing in relief]
[mobile ringing and buzzing]
[woman mumbling over mobile]
[bleats]
[Ella groans]
[sighing]
Huh? Ooh!
[bleats]
Huh?
[exclaims]
[all bleating]
[beeping]
[Ben] Uh-huh.
[both exclaim]
-[Ben chuckles]
-Ah.
[Ben] Hmm.
-[both] Huh?
-[bleating in distance]
[Jin gasping]
[all groaning]
-[Jin groans]
-[Ben] Huh?
[Shaun grunts]
[beeping]
[both] Huh?
[whirring and beeping]
-[Roomba whooshing]
-[Ben yelling]
[Jin gasping]
[Ben groaning]
-[Ben] Whoa!
-[Jin yelps]
[all bleating]
[Shaun gasps]
[chuckles]
[all bleating]
[Ella panting]
[grunting]
[Shirley chuckling] Whoa!
[all yelling]
[Shaun] Whoa!
[all groaning in pain]
[chuckles]
[Ella chuckling]
[Ben grunting]
[Jin groaning]
[Ben] Whoa!
-[grunts]
-[bird chirps]
Huh?
[groans]
[chuckles]
[kisses]
[Shaun grunts]
[all bleating]
[Ella] Hmm.
[grunting and exclaiming]
[all yelling]
[effort grunts]
[Shaun grunts]
[toy squeaks]
Hmm. [bleats]
[boings]
-Aha!
-[all cheering]
Hmph!
[all bleating and groaning]
[bleats]
[all bleating]
-[effort grunts]
-[doorknob rattles]
-[Shaun grunts]
-[wind blowing]
[Shaun gasping]
[bleats]
Hmm.
[dramatic music playing]
[Bitzer gasping]
Er…
[fizzing]
[bottles clattering]
[grunting]
[all grunting]
-[thuds]
-[microwave dings]
[all bleating]
-[exclaims]
-[all yelling]
-[Shaun grunting]
-[The Flock bleating]
Huh?
[gasps]
-[yells]
-[bleats]
[light bulbs smashing]
Oh!
[bleating in panic]
-[light bulbs smashing]
-[Shaun] Oh!
[grunts] Whoa!
[Timmy bleating]
[gasps]
[menacing music playing]
[wind whistling]
[bleats excitedly]
-[fizzing and bubbling]
-Huh?
[giggling] Whoo-hoo!
Ah!
[liquid bubbling and fizzing]
-[Shaun laughs]
-[all cheering]
[liquid bubbling]
[chuckles]
-[Shaun chuckling]
-[bleats]
[sighs in relief]
[Bitzer grunts]
[Timmy's Mother bleating]
[sighs]
-[doorknob rattling]
-[both gasp]
[both gasp]
[wind blowing]
[wind whooshes]
[exclaims]
[both sigh in relief]
[all sighing]
[exclaims]
-[chuckles]
-Aww.
[mumbles]
[both gasping]
[bubbling]
[Ben gasps]
-[hair twangs]
-[both chuckle]
[all sighing contentedly]
[uplifting music playing]
[sighing]
[chuckles]
[bubbling]
[bell ringing in distance]
-Huh?
-[bubbling]
Oh! Ho-ho!
Huh?
Ah! [laughs]
[trumpets]
Oh! [groans]
[all cheering]
[laughing]
[uplifting music playing]
[man] Ho ho ho!
[exclaims]
[bells jingling]
[Santa chuckling] Ho ho ho!
[bleating excitedly]
[sighs]
[bleats]
-[sleigh whooshing]
-[liquid bubbling]
[crowing]
[Shaun chuckling]
-[imitates turkey crowing]
-[chuckles]
[gasps]
[The Farmer humming]
[axe chopping]
[sighs in relief]
[imperceptible]
[cheerful music playing]
[shivering]
[groans and smacks lips]
-[grunts]
-[cracking]
-[The Farmer whistles]
-Huh?
[Bitzer grumbling]
-[grunts and chuckles]
-[gasps]
[panting excitedly]
-[chuckles]
-[grunts and chuckles]
[Shaun] Hmm?
[exclaims]
[gasps]
[Shaun chuckles]
[emotional music playing]
[bleats]
[Shaun sighs]
[all bleating]
[cheering]
[cheers]
["We Wish You a Merry Christmas" playing]
[all sipping]
[all gasping]
[all shuddering]
[all yelling indistinctly]
-[squeaking]
-[all groaning]
-[all exclaim]
-[Bitzer] Hmm.
[all exclaiming]
[Shaun chuckling]
-[both chuckling]
-[glasses clinking]
[upbeat festive music playing]
♪ Can you hear the sounds of all the… ♪
♪ Bells are jingling ♪
♪ Stars are tinkling ♪
♪ Ooh, stars are tinkling ♪
♪ Mmm-mmm ♪